[
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-3-4$$",
        "latexAnswer": "-7"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-3 * (-4)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "12"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-5)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "5"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-(-5))$$",
        "latexAnswer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-(-(-5)))$$",
        "latexAnswer": "5"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$8 - (-9)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "17"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-1 * (-2) * -(-5)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "10"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-3) * (-4)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "-12"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-2 - (-7)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "5"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-8) + (-3)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "5"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-(-2)) * (-3)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "6"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-4 - (-6))$$",
        "latexAnswer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-(-(-3))) * (-2)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-7) - (-(-5))$$",
        "latexAnswer": "2"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-(-5)) + (-(-3))$$",
        "latexAnswer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-2) * -(-3)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-(-(-(-4))))$$",
        "latexAnswer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-(-(-(-(-6)))))$$",
        "latexAnswer": "6"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-(-2) - (-(-3)) + (-4)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "-3"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$-1 * (-2) * -(-5) * (-(-(-2)))$$",
        "latexAnswer": "20"
    }
]
